let questions = [
  {
    "numb": 11,
    "question": "Tree → Frugivorous birds → Hawk represents",
    "answer": "spindle pyramids of numbers",
    "options": [
      "upright pyramid of numbers",
      "inverted pyramid of numbers",
      "spindle pyramids of numbers",
      "dumbbell pyramid of numbers"
    ]
},

{
    "numb": 12,
    "question": "If we all became vegetarians, we'll be able to support our large populations. This can be explained through",
    "answer": "10% rule",
    "options": [
      "10% rule",
      "1% rule",
      "trophic cascade",
      "biodiversity"
    ]
},

{
    "numb": 13,
    "question": "Consider the food chain: Grass → Grasshopper → Frog → Snake → Hawk. As we move up the food chain,",
    "answer": "available energy decreases",
    "options": [
      "available energy decreases",
      "available energy increases",
      "available energy remains the same",
      "available energy is zero everywhere"
    ]
},

{
    "numb": 14,
    "question": "Glacial lakes are typical examples of",
    "answer": "oligotrophic lakes",
    "options": [
      "eutrophic lakes",
      "hypereutrophic lakes",
      "oligotrophic lakes",
      "mesotrophic lakes"
    ]
},

{
    "numb": 15,
    "question": "Trees → Birds → Parasites → Hyperparasites represents",
    "answer": "inverted pyramid of numbers",
    "options": [
      "upright pyramid of numbers",
      "inverted pyramid of numbers",
      "spindle pyramid of numbers",
      "dumbbell pyramid of numbers"
    ]
}
,
{
    "numb": 16,
    "question": "Consider the food chain: Grass → Grasshopper → Frog → Snake → Hawk. In the food chain,",
    "answer": "Frog is consumer and carnivore",
    "options": [
      "Frog is producer",
      "Frog is consumer and carnivore",
      "Frog is consumer and herbivore",
      "Frog is decomposer"
    ]
}
,
{
    "numb": 17,
    "question": "At the compensation point",
    "answer": "photosynthesis = respiration",
    "options": [
      "photosynthesis = respiration",
      "photosynthesis < respiration",
      "photosynthesis > respiration",
      "photosynthesis = 0"
    ]
}
,
{
    "numb": 18,
    "question": "Consider the food chain: Grass → Grasshopper → Frog → Snake → Hawk. In this food chain,",
    "answer": "More number of grasshoppers than hawks can be supported",
    "options": [
      "More number of hawks than grasshoppers can be supported",
      "More number of grasshoppers than hawks can be supported",
      "Equal number of hawks and grasshoppers can be supported",
      "None of these"
    ]
}
,
{
    "numb": 19,
    "question": "Consider the food chain: Grass → Grasshopper → Frog → Snake → Hawk. In this food chain,",
    "answer": "Hawk is consumer and carnivore",
    "options": [
      "Hawk is producer",
      "Hawk is consumer and carnivore",
      "Hawk is consumer and herbivore",
      "Hawk is decomposer"
    ]
}
,
{
    "numb": 20,
    "question": "Net primary productivity is given by",
    "answer": "APAR X LUE",
    "options": [
      "APAR X LUE",
      "APAR + LUE",
      "APAR - LUE",
      "APAR / LUE"
    ]
}
]